quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What port does POP3 operate on?",
        "correct_answer": "110",
        "options": ["139", "112", "110", "120"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following computing models allows the execution of multiple processes on a single processor by having the operating system switch between them without requiring modification to the application?",
        "correct_answer": "Multitasking",
        "options": ["Multitasking", "Multiprocessing", "Multiprogramming", "Multithreading"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does LDAPS operate on?",
        "correct_answer": "636",
        "options": ["633", "636", "366", "663"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What process is typically used to ensure data security for workstations that are being removed from service but that will be resold or otherwise reused?",
        "correct_answer": "Sanitisation",
        "options": ["Destruction", "Erasing", "Sanitisation", "Clearing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What process adds a header and a footer to data received at each layer of the OSI model?",
        "correct_answer": "Encapsulation",
        "options": ["Attribution", "Encapsulation", "TCP Wrapping", "Data Hiding"]
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the operating protection ring model, what ring contains user programs and applications?",
        "correct_answer": "Ring 3",
        "options": ["Ring 3", "Ring 2", "Ring 1", "Ring 0"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of error occurs when a valid subject using a biometric authenticator is not authenticated?",
        "correct_answer": "Type 1 error",
        "options": ["Type 2 error", "Type 3 error", "Type 1 error", "Type 4 error"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does NNTP use?",
        "correct_answer": "119",
        "options": ["161", "123", "119", "143"]
    },
    {
        "question": "When evaluating biometric devices, what is another term used to describe the equal error rate?",
        "correct_answer": "CER",
        "options": ["FAR", "FRR", "CER", "EER"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the IP Header, which Protocol Number identifies TCP?",
        "correct_answer": "6",
        "options": ["1", "4", "6", "13"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is an attack vector?",
        "correct_answer": "Malware",
        "options": ["Malware", "A weak password", "Script kiddie", "Loss of intellectual property"]
    }
]
